var HTMLquestions = [

    {
        question: "HTML is what type of language ?",
        choices: ["Scripting Language", "Markup Language", "Programming Language", "Network Protocol"],
        answer: 2

    },

    {
        question: "HTML uses :",
        choices: ["User defined tags", "Pre-specified tags", "Fixed tags defined by the language", "Tags only for linking"],
        answer: 3

    },
    {
        question: "The year in which HTML was first proposed _______.",
        choices: ["1990", "1980", "2000", "1995"],
        answer: 1

    },
    {
        question: "Apart from <b> tag, what other tag makes text bold ?",
        choices: ["fat", "strong", "black", "emp"],
        answer: 2

    },
    {/*5*/
        question: "How can you make a bulleted list with numbers? ",
        choices: ["dl", "ol", "list", "ul"],
        answer: 2

    },
    {
        question: "What tag is used to display a picture in a HTML page?",
        choices: ["picture", "image", "pic", "img"],
        answer: 4

    },
    {
        question: "HTML web pages can be read and rendered by _________.",
        choices: ["Compiler", "Server", "Web Browser", "Interpreter"],
        answer: 3

    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following is not a browser ?",
        choices: ["Microsofts Bing", "Netscape Navigator", "Mozilla Firefox", "Opera"],
        answer: 1

    },
    {
        question: "HTML tags are surrounded by which type of brackets.",
        choices: ["Curly", "Round", "Squart", "Angle"],
        answer: 4

    },
    {/*10*/
        question: "Tags and test that are not directly displayed on the page are written in _____ section.",
        choices: ["head", "title", "body", "html"],
        answer: 1

    }

];